http://www.iw5edi.com/about/privacy-info

Live Stream
Perchè (Why) in English ?
Metric Conversion Table
Sound Card Interfacing for RTTY,
W4TI Rotor Installation
iw5edi.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should always check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information: name, contact information including email address, etc.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: to facilitate a specific request on our site, for example, to post a comment on our blog or to subscribe to our email feed. All emails or feed subscriptions from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
Â Â Â  How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file placed on your computerâ€™s hard drive which helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Third parties such as our advertisers may also place cookies on your browser in the course of serving ads to you.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.
Â Â Â  Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Â Â Â  How to contact us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our blog.
Leave a comment Cancel replyYour email address will not be published.Comment Name
Email
Website
Notify me of new posts by email.
Please input symbols from picture
IW5EDI Simone
Licensed Amateur Radio operator in 1996 as IW5EDI, active member of ARI Firenze and ARRL
Class 1970, married with two childrens, love experimenting and antenna home-brewing. IT System Engineer, recently started having fun with morse code and Raspberry Pi
IW5EDI Simone
This Blog is mainly dedicated to Amateur Radio (Ham radio) and contains external articles and personal esperiences.
What is Amateur Radio ?
More Ham Radio Links
My Content
Antenna Projects
RadioAnnunci.it
Mercatino Radioamatoriale
Sponsor
Categories
Articles (117)
Antenna Theory (9)
DXing (1)
How to (7)
shortwave (5)
Company and Products (1)
DXing (13)
QSLing (4)
Equipment (96)
Antenna (64)
Software Defined Radio (6)
Featured (27)
Ham Radio Events (25)
Ham Radio News (1)
Ham Radio Software (23)
HamRadio (84)
Ham Radio 2.0 (16)
How to (3)
Radio Scanning (6)
Homebrew (108)
HF Antennas (63)
Raspberry Pi (1)
UHF Antenna (10)
VHF Antennas (27)
Photos (4)
Short News (4)
Video (4)
CommentsUli on About meBob on GAP Titan DX – TuningSimone on GAP Titan DX – TuningBob on GAP Titan DX – TuningSimone on Assembling GAP Titan DX Antenna
Ham Radio Blog – IW5EDI Simone JN53OR
This site use cookies to ensure you the best experience in navigation. If you continue to use this site it is assumed that you are happy with it.OkRead more
